[
  {
    "question" : "What gas is used in the laser cutter?",
    "incorrect" : ["argon", "helium", "hydrogen"],
    "correct" : "carbon dioxide"
  },
  {
    "question" : "How is the quizmaster communicating with the cup bots?",
    "incorrect" : ["WiFi", "Bluetooth", "USB"],
    "correct" : "Radio"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What does FDM stand for?",
    "incorrect" : ["full design modelling", "fun design making", "factoring detail modelling"],
    "correct" : "fused deposition modelling"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What kind of manufacturing is 3D printing?",
    "incorrect" : ["subtractive", "divisive", "attractive"],
    "correct" : "additive"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Your design has to perfect before making it in the Eagle Lab. True or false?",
    "incorrect" : ["true"],
    "correct" : "false"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What does LASER stand for?",
    "incorrect" : ["large and scary erratic radiation","light and sound erosion radiation","light and spark electric radiation"],
    "correct" : "light amplification by stimulated emission of radiation"
  },
  {
    "question" : "The Eagle Lab is only for technology products. True or false?",
    "incorrect" : ["true"],
    "correct" : "false"
  },
  {
    "question" : "How many Eagle Labs do we have in the UK?",
    "incorrect" : ["5", "10", "25"],
    "correct" : "14"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What year did our Salford Eagle Lab open?",
    "incorrect" : ["2012", "2014", "2017"],
    "correct" : "2016"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Eagle Labs is a space to create, innovate and...?",
    "incorrect" : ["make stuff", "help", "build"],
    "correct" : "Grow"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Our Salford Eagle Lab is located in?",
    "incorrect" : ["WhiteSpace", "Avenue HQ", "Codebase"],
    "correct" : "The Landing"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Barclays Eagle Labs celebrated a birthday last week, what was it?",
    "incorrect" : ["1st Birthday", "3rd Birthday", "4th Birthday"],

    "correct" : "2nd Birthday"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Subtract the year the Manchester Ship Canal was opened from the birth of MediaCityUK and add the amount of silver coffee pods in the lab, what do you get?",
    "incorrect" : ["107","132","147"],
    "correct" : "125"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Our Eagle labs has a cool big brother that help communities to become more tech savvy, what are they called?",
    "incorrect" : ["Digital Hawks", "Computer Eagles", "binary birds"],
    "correct" : "Digital Eagles"
  },
  {
  "question" : "Complete the phrase from a few stickers around the lab, Do not unplug doing a ...",
  "incorrect" : ["update","banana","james","work thing"],
  "correct" : "science"
  },
  {
    "question" : "When was MediaCityUK born?",
    "incorrect" : ["2017","2006","2005"],
    "correct" : "2007"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What's the blueprint in the picture frame show?",
    "incorrect" : ["game pad","joycon","death star","arcade machine"],
    "correct" : "joystick"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What's the Eagle Lab Salford Twitter handle?",
    "incorrect" : ["eagle_lab","eaglelabsalford","elsalford","eagle_lab_sal","eagle_labs_salford","eagle_lab_salford"],
    "correct" : "eagle_labs_sal"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What flavour are the Pi's in the lab?",
    "incorrect" : ["strawberry","blueberry","apple"],
    "correct" : "raspberry"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What does the word robot mean, from the Czech word robota?",
    "incorrect" : ["mechanical machine","non-human","worker"],
    "correct" : "forced labor"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Everyday the human brain generates more electrical impulses than all the telephone wires, in the world, put together. True or False?",
    "incorrect" : ["false"],
    "correct" : "true"
  },
  {
    "question" : "The human brain can power a light bulb. True or False?",
    "incorrect" : ["false"],
    "correct" : "true"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Exercise makes you smarter. True or False?",
    "incorrect" : ["false"],
    "correct" : "true"
  },
  {
    "question" : "A pixel is the smallest controllable element on a screen. True or False?",
    "incorrect" : ["false"],
    "correct" : "true"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Pac-Man, the original arcade game was released in the 1970’s. True or False?",
    "incorrect" : ["true"],
    "correct" : "false"
  },
  {
    "question" : "ROM stands for Read Only Machine. True or False?",
    "incorrect" : ["true"],
    "correct" : "false"
  },
  {
    "question" : "A 3D printer extrudes plastic at temperatures below 180˚C. True or False?",
    "incorrect" : ["true"],
    "correct" : "false"
  },
  {
    "question" : "A Micro:bit has 24 red LED lights. True or False?",
    "incorrect" : ["true"],
    "correct" : "false"
  },
  {
    "question" : "How many buttons does a Micro:bit have?",
    "incorrect" : ["1","2","4"],
    "correct" : "3"
  },
  {
    "question" : "A Micro:bit has WiFi. True or False?",
    "incorrect" : ["true"],
    "correct" : "false"
  },
  {
    "question" : "A Micro:bit can tell you the temperature of the room it’s in. True or False?",
    "incorrect" : ["false"],
    "correct" : "true"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What year was Google founded in?",
    "incorrect" : ["1997","1987","2007"],
    "correct" : "1998"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What year was the first iPhone released?",
    "incorrect" : ["2005","2006","2008"],
    "correct" : "2007"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What does 3D stand for?",
    "incorrect" : ["three-doors","third-depth","three-amigos"],
    "correct" : "three-dimensional"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What does CAD stand for?",
    "incorrect" : ["Computer-Assisted Design","Computer-Advanced Design","Computer-Aware Design"],
    "correct" : "Computer-Aided Design"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What file formats does Eagle Labs generally use for 3D printing?",
    "incorrect" : ["3DP","PNG","JPG"],
    "correct" : "STL"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What technology sector does Eagle Lab Salford focus on?",
    "incorrect" : ["LawTech","Artificial Intelligence","FinTech"],
    "correct" : "MedTech"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Potentially, how much per minute of surgery could 3D printing save the NHS?",
    "incorrect" : ["£40","£50","£70"],
    "correct" : "£60"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What does AR stand for?",
    "incorrect" : ["Average Reality","Assisted Reality","Augmented Rationality"],
    "correct" : "Augmented Reality"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What does IoT stand for?",
    "incorrect" : ["Interesting Otherworldly Thoughts","Investment of Things","Illuminating of Technology"],
    "correct" : "Internet of Things"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What does VR stand for?",
    "incorrect" : ["Various Reality","Virtual Robotics","Volumetric Reasoning"],
    "correct" : "Virtual Reality"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What does LED stand for?",
    "incorrect" : ["Light Evolving Dictation","Lemon Eating Dog","Long Energy Device"],
    "correct" : "Light Emitting Diode"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What does GPS stand for?",
    "incorrect" : ["Global Pointing System","Grid Pixel System","Geographical Photon Support"],
    "correct" : "Global Positioning System"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Firefox, Opera, Chrome, Safari and Explorer are types of what?",
    "incorrect" : ["Spaceships","Cars","Suits"],
    "correct" : "Web browsers"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Solar power generates electricity from what source?",
    "incorrect" : ["The Moon","Street Lights","Plant energy"],
    "correct" : "The Sun"
  },
  {
    "question" : "In computing, keyboards are used as input devices. True or false?",
    "incorrect" : ["False"],
    "correct" : "True"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What does the abbreviation WWW stand for?",
    "incorrect" : ["World Wrestling Wonder","Wandering Wizard Wand","Working World Watch"],
    "correct" : "World Wide Web"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Nintendo was founded after the year 1900. True or false?",
    "incorrect" : ["True"],
    "correct" : "False"
  },
  {
    "question" : "In terms of computing, what does CPU stand for?",
    "incorrect" : ["Computer Power Unit","Capital Production Unicorn","Common Programming Unification"],
    "correct" : "Central Processing Unit"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Gold is not a good conductor of electricity? True or false?",
    "incorrect" : ["True"],
    "correct" : "False"
  },
  {
    "question" : "In electricity, voltage is measured in volts while current is measured in what?",
    "incorrect" : ["Curts","Percentage","Degrees"],
    "correct" : "Amps"
  },
  {
    "question" : "DB in computer abbreviation usually means?",
    "incorrect" : ["Data Bytes","Defence Bots","Dog Biscuits"],
    "correct" : "Database"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Hackers who attempt to do good through hacking are called what?",
    "incorrect" : ["black hats", "red hats", "green hats"],
    "correct" : "white hats"
  },
 {
    "question" : "In computing what is a Nibble?",
    "incorrect" : ["8 bits", "1 bit", "1/2 bit"],
    "correct" : "4 bits"
  },
 {
    "question" : "Metadata means?",
    "incorrect" : ["mega data", "informational data", "metalogical data"],
    "correct" : "data about data"
  },
 {
    "question" : "What is a magnetic strip?",
    "incorrect" : ["Used to stick stuff to the fridge"],
    "correct" : "A way of storing data into credit and debit cards"
  },
 {
    "question" : "In computer science what is CLI?",
    "incorrect" : ["computer language interface", "common language input"],
    "correct" : "command line interface"
  },
 {
    "question" : "In computer science what is GUI?",
    "incorrect" : ["general user interface", "gaming user interface"],
    "correct" : "graphical user interface"
  },
 {
    "question" : "Which of these is most likely to use Haptic Feedback?",
    "incorrect" : ["a shower", "a fire alarm"],
    "correct" : "a game controller"
  },
 {
    "question" : "Which of these is not an operating system (OS)?",
    "incorrect" : ["iOS", "Linux", "Windows"],
    "correct" : "ApplePieOS"
  },
 {
    "question" : "A Blue-ray Disc can hold up to?",
    "incorrect" : ["30GB", "40GB"],
    "correct" : "50GB"
  },
  {
    "question" : "The image file PNG format stands for?",
    "incorrect" : ["Printable Network Graphics", "Pictures Not Graphics"],
    "correct" : "Portable Network Graphics"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Which of these is an example of a Massive Multiplayer Online Role Play Games (MMORPG)?",
    "incorrect" : ["Mario Kart 8", "Candy Crush Saga"],
    "correct" : "World of Warcraft"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Who was the first British astronaut?",
    "incorrect" : ["Tim Peake", "Thomas Kane", "Neil Armstrong"],
    "correct" : "Helen Sharman"
  }
]
